Register of the Sir Karl Raimund Popper Papers, 1928-1995
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE II, 1932-1995 (Box 512, Box 512-568)
  - Osterreichische Musikzeitschrift, 1990-1991 (Folder 555: 4)
  - Osterreichisches College, 1985-1992 (Folder 555: 5)
  - Osterreichischer Rundfunk (ORF), 1972-1992 (Folder 555: 6)
  - Oswalt, Walter, 1993-1994 (Folder 555: 7)
  - Ourisson, Guy, 1992 (Folder 555: 8)
  - Oxford University Press (Adam Hodgkin, N. W. Wilson) mainly re Objective Knowledge
    - 1970-1979 (Folder 555: 9)
    - 1980-1990 (Folder 555: 10)
  - Pace, Norman, 1987 (Folder 555: 11)
  - Pahler, Klaus, 1985-1990 (Folder 555: 12)
  - Panchenko, Dmitri, 1991-1993 (Folder 555: 13)
  - Pandit, Giridhari, 1987-1992 (Folder 555: 14)
  - Papadaki, Irene, mainly re Greek translations of Karl Popper's works (Box 556)
    - 1979-1989 (Folder 556: 1)
    - 1990-1994 (Folder 556: 2)
  - Parikh, Suresh, 1962 (Folder 556: 3)
  - Parton, Hugh Noble and Jean, 1962-1991 (Folder 556: 4)
  - Parusnikova, Zuzana, 1988 (Folder 556: 5)
  - Pasquinelli, Alberto, 1954-1994 (Folder 556: 6)
  - Passmore, John Arthur, 1954-1979 (Folder 556: 7)
  - Patel, I. G., 1987-1989 (Folder 556: 8)
  - Patel, Natubhai K., 1990 (Folder 556: 9)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1989 (Folder 556: 10)
  - Peng, Dean, 1989 (Folder 556: 11)
  - Penguin Books Ltd. (Michael Dover, Ted Honderich), 1978 (Folder 556: 12)
  - Pera, Marcello, 1979-1991 (Folder 556: 13)
  - Percival, Ray, 1989 (Folder 556: 14)
  - Perutz, Max, 1986-1994 (Folder 556: 15)
  - Peters, Richard, 1973 (Folder 556: 16)
  - Peters, Vera, 1994 (Folder 556: 17)
  - Petersen, Arne Friemuth and Marie-Francoise, 1972-1991 (Folder 556: 18)
  - Petroni, Angelo, 1985-1992 (Folder 557: 1)
  - Peyrefitte, Alain, 1985 (Folder 557: 2)
  - Pezzimenti, Rocco, 1984-1993 (Folder 557: 3)
  - Pfaundler, Wolfgang, 1975-1979 (Folder 557: 4)
  - Pfender, Ruth, 1988-1990 (Folder 557: 5)
  - Pflughaupt, Knut-Rainer, 1985-1986 (Folder 557: 6)
  - Philip, Winifred, 1988-1994 (Folder 557: 7)
  - Phipps, Thomas E., Jr., 1974-1990 (Folder 557: 8)
  - Pickel, Andreas, 1994 (Folder 557: 9)
  - Pietschmann, Herbert, 1975-1976 (Folder 557: 10)
  - Pizano, Diego, 1977-1978 (Folder 557: 11)
  - Plamenatz, John, 1952 (Folder 557: 12)
  - Platnick, Norman I., 1979-1988 (Folder 557: 13)
  - Plenum Publishing Co., 1989-1990 (Folder 557: 14)
  - Pocock, Philip J., 1959-1993 (Folder 557: 15)
  - Podlaha, M. F., 1985 (Folder 557: 16)
  - Pogorzaly, Maizena, 1988-1989 (Folder 557: 17)
  - Pohlen, Manfred,., 1994 (Folder 557: 18)
    Includes correspondence with Margarethe Bautz-Holzherr
  - Polish Scientific Publishers PWN Ltd., 1991-1993 (Folder 557: 19)
  - Pollak, Guido, 1990 (Folder 557: 20)
  - Pongratz, Christl, 1987 (Folder 557: 21)
  - Pontificia Academia Scientiarum (Renato Dardozzi), 1987-1988 (Folder 557: 22)
  - Poole, H. W., 1955-1967 (Folder 557: 23)
  - Pope, Vivian, 1975-1985 (Folder 557: 24)
  - Poschke, Peter, 1987-1988 (Folder 557: 25)
  - Poser, Hans, 1994 (Folder 558: 1)
  - Potter, Billet, 1972 (Folder 558: 2)
  - Powell, J. Enoch, 1991 (Folder 558: 3)
  - Princeton University Press (Datus C. Smith, Jr., Roy E. Thomas, Carol Orr), mainly re The Open Society and Its Enemies
    - 1946-1950 (Folder 558: 4)
    - 1967-1984 (Folder 558: 5)
  - Prirogine, Ilya, 1987-1988 (Folder 558: 6)
  - Probst, David Karl, 1965-1974 (Folder 558: 7)
  - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, 1987-1992 (Folder 558: 8)
  - Prokhovnik, Simon J., 1990 (Folder 558: 9)
  - Publicacoes Don Quixote (Joao Carlos Alvim),, re Portuguese edition of Postscript to the Logic of Scientific Discovery, 1986-1993 (Folder 558: 10)
  - Publico, 1990-1991 (Folder 558: 11)
  - Pyke, Steve, 1990 (Folder 558: 12)
  - Qiu, Renzong, 1990-1991 (Folder 558: 13)
  - Quinton, Anthony, 1965-1978 (Folder 558: 14)
  - R. Piper & Co. Verlag (Hans Rossner),, mainly re German edition of The Self and Its Brain, 1972-1994 (Folder 559: 1)
  - Radiotelevisione della Svizzera italiana (RTSI), 1977-1991 (Folder 559: 2)
  - Radnitzky, Gerard, 1975-1992 (Folder 559: 3)
  - Ragep, F. Jamil, 1993 (Folder 559: 4)
  - Rasmussen, Edgar Tranekjear, 1956-1957 (Folder 559: 5)
  - Rathman, Mujeeb, 1988 (Folder 559: 6)
  - Rationalist Press Association, 1973-1985 (Folder 559: 7)
  - Read, Herbert, 1944 (Folder 559: 8)
  - Redent, Ursula, 1991 (Folder 559: 9)
  - Redhead, Michael, 1983-1994 (Folder 559: 10)
  - Redman, Deborah A., 1990 (Folder 559: 11)
  - Reed, Alan, 1973-1976 (Folder 559: 12)
  - Rehlingen, Fritz von, 1989 (Folder 559: 13)
  - Reikl, Johann, 1987 (Folder 559: 14)
  - Reinisch, Helga, 1987 (Folder 559: 15)
  - Reiss, Hans S., 1973-1994 (Folder 559: 16)
  - Repubblica, 1990 (Folder 559: 17)
  - Revue internationale de philosophie, 1969-1971 (Folder 559: 18)
  - Richthofen, Hermann, 1991-1993 (Folder 559: 19)
  - Riedl, Rupert, 1975-1990 (Folder 559: 20)
  - Rigato, Alberto, 1986 (Folder 559: 21)
  - Roberts, Lionel, 1958-1974 (Folder 559: 22)
  - Roner, Rosemarie, 1989-1994 (Folder 559: 23)
  - Rossner, Hans, 1978-1970 (Folder 559: 24)
  - Roth, George E. and Edith, 1979 (Folder 559: 25)
  - Rothman, Kenneth J., 1988 (Folder 560: 1)
  - Routledge & Kegan Paul (Norman Franklin, T. Murray Ragg)
    - 1944-1959 (Folder 560: 2)
    - 1968-1970 (Folder 560: 3)
    - 1971-1979 (Folder 560: 4)
    - 1980-1990 (Folder 560: 5)
  - Rowe, James, 1986 (Folder 560: 6)
  - Rowe Radcliffe Solicitors (formerly Weightman Rowe)
    - 1988-1989 (Folder 560: 7)
    - 1990-1991 (Folder 560: 8)
  - Royal Society, 1985-1994 (Folder 561: 1)
  - Rozeboom, William W., 1969 (Folder 561: 2)
  - Runnegar, Bruce, 1989 (Folder 561: 3)
  - Russell, Bertrand, Lord, 1936-1960 (Folder 561: 4)
  - S. Fischer Verlag, 1992 (Folder 561: 5)
  - Sabra, Abdel Hamid Ibrahim and Nancy, 1959-1993 (Folder 561: 6)
  - Sacher, Peter, 1993-1994 (Folder 561: 7)
  - Sadovsky, Vadim N., 1983-1994 (Folder 561: 8)
  - Safaiee, Soheila, 1987-1988 (Folder 561: 9)
  - Saggiatore, 1985 (Folder 561: 10)
  - Salamun, Kurt, 1976-1987 (Folder 561: 11)
  - Sallam, Henriko, 1991-1993 (Folder 561: 12)
  - Sallinger, Hermann, 1986-1987 (Folder 561: 13)
  - Sallows, Lee, 1979 (Folder 561: 14)
  - Salzer, Martin, 1983-1989 (Folder 561: 15)
  - Samet, Sigfrido, 1994 (Folder 561: 16)
  - Samuel, Lord, 1956-1962 (Folder 561: 17)
  - Scerri, Eric, 1993 (Folder 561: 18)
  - Schafer, Lothar, 1987-1988 (Folder 561: 19)
  - Schatz, Roland, 1987-1993 (Folder 561: 20)
  - Schellenbacher, Manfred, 1983-1987 (Folder 561: 21)
  - Schiff, Erich and Mary, 1974-1993 (Folder 561: 22)
  - Schiff, Otto and Dietlinde, 1990-1993 (Folder 561: 23)
  - Schilling, Klaus, 1991 (Folder 561: 24)
  - Schimanko, Dora, 1985-1994 (Folder 561: 25)
  - Schmidt, Helmut, 1984-1994 (Folder 562: 1)
  - Schmidt, Hermann Josef, 1991-1994 (Folder 562: 2)
  - Schoeck, Helmut and Margaret, 1987-1993 (Folder 562: 3)
  - Scholter, Siegfried, 1985-1993 (Folder 562: 4)
  - Schonborn, Felizitas von, 1992-1993 (Folder 562: 5)
  - Schreiber, Alfred, 1976 (Folder 562: 6)
  - Schrodinger, Erwin, 1950-1954 (Folder 562: 7)
  - Schroeder-Heister, Peter, 1988-1990 (Folder 562: 8)
  - Schwartz, Pedro, 1959-1994 (Folder 562: 9)
  - Schwarz-Schilling, Marie-Luise, 1986-1987 (Folder 562: 10)
  - Schwyzer-Shuh, Elsa and Christl, 1986-1992 (Folder 562: 11)
  - Scruton, Roger, 1987 (Folder 562: 12)
  - Searchinger, Gene, 1978-1979 (Folder 562: 13)
  - Seidel, Harald, 1985-1987 (Folder 562: 14)
  - Seiffert, August, 1979-1985 (Folder 562: 15)
  - Seiffert, Helmut, 1979-1988 (Folder 562: 16)
  - Selfen, Jan, 1978 (Folder 562: 17)
  - Sellars, Wilfred, 1962 (Folder 562: 18)
  - Selleri, Franco, 1984-1990 (Folder 562: 19)
  - Semelidis, Vanias, 1990-1991 (Folder 562: 20)
  - Serkin, Rudi and Irene, 1988-1991 (Folder 562: 21)
  - Settle, Thomas W., 1969-1974 (Folder 562: 22)
  - Shaked, Rahav, 1985 (Folder 562: 23)
  - Shearmur, Jeremy, 1975 (Folder 562: 24)
  - Shelley, Julian, 1976-1979 (Folder 562: 25)
  - Simkin, Colin, 1959-1990 (Folder 563: 1)
  - Singh, Jitendra and Kusum, 1957-1988 (Folder 563: 2)
  - Skagestad, Peter, 1978 (Folder 563: 3)
  - Skarsgard, Lars, 1958 (Folder 563: 4)
  - Smeenk, Ben, 1993 (Folder 563: 5)
  - Smith, N. C. S., 1993 (Folder 563: 6)
  - Smithers, David W., 1964-1979 (Folder 563: 7)
  - Soares, Mario and Maria Barroso, 1986-1993 (Folder 563: 8)
  - Society for the Protection of Science and Learning, 1958 (Folder 563: 9)
  - Society of Authors (Mark Le Fanu), 1989 (Folder 563: 10)
  - Solo, Robert, 1955-1958 (Folder 563: 11)
  - Solti, Georg, 1992-1993 (Folder 563: 12)
  - Soreth, Marion, 1990-1994 (Folder 563: 13)
  - Sorman, Guy, 1987-1990 (Folder 563: 14)
  - Soros, George, 1975-1994 (Folder 563: 15)
  - Souvenir Press (Ernest Hecht), 1972-1976 (Folder 563: 16)
  - Spearman, Diana, 1958-1990 (Folder 563: 17)
  - Spengler, Herbert, 1973-1991 (Folder 563: 18)
  - Spiegel (Helmut Gumnior), 1975-1992 (Folder 563: 19)
  - Spinner, Helmut, 1971-1978 (Folder 564: 1)
  - Spitzer, Robert, 1989-1990 (Folder 564: 2)
  - Springer Verlag (Monika Brendel, Laurel Fremgen-Hamilton, Heinz Gotze, Birgit Hadler, Paul B. Mayer, K. Teichmann) mainly re The Self and Its Brain
    - 1976-1977 (Folder 564: 3)
    - 1978-1979 (Folder 564: 4)
    - 1980-1994 (Folder 564: 5)
  - Stachel, Peter, 1991 (Folder 564: 6)
  - Stadler, Friedrich, 1978-1992 (Folder 564: 7)
  - Stamatis, Georg, 1987 (Folder 564: 8)
  - Stanley, T. D., 1988 (Folder 564: 9)
  - Starbatty, Joachim, 1989-1992 (Folder 564: 10)
  - Steele, Edward J., 1979-1992 (Folder 564: 11)
  - Steele, Gordon, 1975-1993 (Folder 564: 12)
  - Steinkopff, Gero, 1988-1989 (Folder 564: 13)
  - Stern, 1980-1981 (Folder 564: 14)
  - Stopes-Roe, H. V., 1968 (Folder 564: 15)
  - Strauss, Franz Josef, 1988 (Folder 564: 16)
  - Streissler, Erich, 1968 (Folder 564: 17)
  - Studio-Film GmbH, 1972 (Folder 564: 18)
  - Stupoff, Rossen, 1993 (Folder 564: 19)
  - Suarez-Iniguez, Enrique, 1991-1994 (Folder 565: 1)
  - Suhrkamp Verlag, 1966-1978 (Folder 565: 2)
  - Sweet & Maxwell Ltd., 1994-1995 (Folder 565: 3)
  - Tabbush, S. J., 1985-1987 (Folder 565: 4)
  - Taylor, Angus, 1988-1989 (Folder 565: 5)
  - Tessmer, Holger, 1991 (Folder 565: 6)
  - Thatcher, Margaret, 1989 (Folder 565: 7)
  - Themel, Cathleen, 1994 (Folder 565: 8)
  - Thoemmes Antiquarian Books Ltd., 1988-1994 (Folder 565: 9)
  - Thorpe, Adrian, 1992 (Folder 565: 10)
  - Thorpe, William, 1972-1978 (Folder 565: 11)
  - Times (London), 1987-1993 (Folder 565: 12)
  - Times Higher Education Supplement, 1978 (Folder 565: 13)
  - Times Literary Supplement, 1975-1985 (Folder 565: 14)
  - Topitsch, Ernst, 1958-1976 (Folder 565: 15)
  - Topolski, Feliks, 1956 (Folder 565: 16)
  - Travaglia, Sergio, 1986 (Folder 565: 17)
  - Treplin, Lore, 1987 (Folder 565: 18)
  - Troidl, Hans, 1988-1993 (Folder 565: 19)
  - Trouble, Michel, 1993 (Folder 565: 20)
  - Trout, J. D., 1990 (Folder 565: 21)
  - Truesdell, Clifford, 1973-1987 (Folder 565: 22)
  - Tubman, Quentin, 1978-1985 (Folder 565: 23)
  - Tullock, Gordon, 1957-1992 (Folder 565: 24)
  - Uitgeverij Het Spectrum (Barbara Richwel, Bastiaan Willink),, re Dutch editions of The Poverty of Historicism and Unended Quest, 1974-1977 (Folder 565: 25)
  - Uitgeverij Kok Agora, 1992-1993 (Folder 565: 26)
  - Ungar, Georges, 1976 (Folder 566: 1)
  - Universitat Duisburg, 1986-1987 (Folder 566: 2)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1949-1992 (Folder 566: 3)
  - University of London, 1963-1992 (Folder 566: 4)
  - University of Otago, 1945 (Folder 566: 5)
  - University of Salford, 1976 (Folder 566: 6)
  - University of Sydney, 1945 (Folder 566: 7)
  - Urban, G. R., 1990 (Folder 566: 8)
  - Vallecchi Editore, 1991-1993 (Folder 566: 9)
  - Verdan, Andre, 1985-1991 (Folder 566: 10)
  - Verdugo, Carlos, 1978-1993 (Folder 566: 11)
  - Verlag Kiepenheuer & Witsch, 1963-1967 (Folder 566: 12)
  - Verlag Moritz Diesterweg, 1986 (Folder 566: 13)
  - Verlag Ullstein, 1990-1992 (Folder 566: 14)
  - Verlagsgruppe Bertelsmann, 1985-1986 (Folder 566: 15)
  - Verrecchio, Anacleto, 1986-1987 (Folder 566: 16)
  - Vigier, Jean-Pierre, 1981-1990 (Folder 566: 17)
  - Vittorio Klostermann Verlag, 1978-1979 (Folder 566: 18)
  - Vlastos, Gregory, 1966-1972 (Folder 566: 19)
  - Vogels, Godfried, 1989 (Folder 566: 20)
  - Wachter, Michael, 1987-1991 (Folder 566: 21)
  - Wachtershauser, Gunter, 1984-1994 (Folder 566: 22)
  - Wadlinger, Robert L., 1985-1990 (Folder 566: 23)
  - Wahl, Henning von, 1986-1989 (Folder 567: 1)
  - Waldheim, Kurt, 1987 (Folder 567: 2)
  - Walsh, James, 1987-1988 (Folder 567: 3)
  - Walter, Nora, 1992 (Folder 567: 4)
  - Wasserman, Benno, 1990 (Folder 567: 5)
  - Watkins, John, 1955-1990 (Folder 567: 6)
  - Wehler, Joachim, 1990-1991 (Folder 567: 7)
  - Weingartner, Paul, 1966-1992 (Folder 567: 8)
  - Weir, Gillian, 1990-1992 (Folder 567: 9)
  - Weisskopf, Victor, 1958 (Folder 567: 10)
  - Weizsacker, Richard von, 1984-1992 (Folder 567: 11)
  - Welt, 1988-1992 (Folder 567: 12)
  - Wenzel, Karl Egbert, 1990-1991 (Folder 567: 13)
  - Werkmeister, W. H., 1962 (Folder 567: 14)
  - Werner, M.-E., 1985 (Folder 567: 15)
  - Wesley, John Paul, 1986-1992 (Folder 567: 16)
  - Wette, Edward, 1962-1974 (Folder 567: 17)
  - Wettersten, John, 1978-1994 (Folder 567: 18)
  - Whitrow, Gerald J., 1953 (Folder 567: 19)
  - Wiener, Philip P., 1975-1976 (Folder 567: 20)
  - Wiener Singakademie, 1992-1993 (Folder 567: 21)
  - William Hodge & Co. Ltd., 1947-1954 (Folder 567: 22)
  - Wilson, Colin Henry, 1987-1990 (Folder 567: 23)
  - Wisdom, John O., 1955-1993 (Folder 567: 24)
  - Wittmann, Wolfgang, 1988 (Folder 567: 25)
  - Wivel, Peter, 1990 (Folder 567: 26)
  - Woese, Carl R., 1987-1991 (Folder 567: 27)
  - Wollheim, Richard, 1954-1955 (Folder 568: 1)
  - Woltersdorf, Gunter, 1986 (Folder 568: 2)
  - Woodger, J. H., 1958-1978 (Folder 568: 3)
  - Workers' Educational Association, 1959-1960 (Folder 568: 4)
  - World Affairs, 1986 (Folder 568: 5)
  - Yourgrau, Wolfgang, 1958-1978 (Folder 568: 6)
  - Zanotti, Gabriel, 1994 (Folder 568: 7)
  - Zanzi, Luigi, 1987 (Folder 568: 8)
  - Zeit, 1989 (Folder 568: 9)
  - Zippelins, Reinhard, 1990-1991 (Folder 568: 10)
  - Zorzan, Nicola, 1993 (Folder 568: 11)
  - Zycha, Harald, 1988 (Folder 568: 12)
- BIOGRAPHICAL FILE II, 1936-1994 (Box 568-573)
  Articles, autobiographical sketch, awards, bibliographies, biographical data, clippings, contracts, copyright certificates, correspondence, honorary degrees, printed matter, and speeches, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Articles and clippings about or mentioning Karl Popper, 1973-1998 (Folder 568: 13)
  - Autobiographical sketch (Folder 568: 14)
  - Awards,., 1964-1984 (Folder 568: 15)
  - Bibliographies (Folder 568: 16)
  - Biographical data (Folder 568: 17)
  - Contracts,., 1965-1983 (Folder 568: 18)
  - Copyright certificates,., 1946-1978 (Folder 569: 1)
  - Honorary degrees
    - University of Chicago,., 1962 December 14 (Folder 569: 2)
      Presentation statement and correspondence
    - University of Canterbury,., 1973 May 5 (Folder 569: 3)
      Program
    - University of Oxford,., 1982 June 23 (Folder 569: 4)
      Printed copy of addresses, program, and correspondence
    - University of London,., 1986 October 15 (Folder 569: 5)
      Typescript of Orator's speech, program, and correspondence
  - Speeches about Karl Popper,., 1992-1995 (Folder 569: 6)
    Includes addresses by Ernst Gombrich and Vaclav Havel. Printed copies and correspondence
  - Subject file
    - Austrian citizenship. (Folder 569: 7)
      Correspondence
    - Birthday celebrations
      - Eighty-fifth, 1987
        - Correspondence (Folder 569: 8-9)
        - Clippings (Folder 569: 10-11)
      - Ninetieth, 1992
        - Correspondence (Folder 570: 1-3)
        - Clipping (Folder 570: 4)
    - British nationality (Folder 570: 5)
    - Companionship of Honour
      - Letters of congratulation (Folder 570: 6)
      - Clippings (Folder 570: 7)
    - Death
      - Letters of condolence (Folder 570: 8-9)
      - Memorial speeches (Folder 571: 1)
      - Obituaries (Folder 571: 2-6)
      - Obituaries (Contd.) (Folder 572: 1)
    - Family genealogy (Folder 572: 2)
    - Knighthood
      - Clippings (Folder 572: 3)
      - Correspondence
        - General (Folder 572: 4)
        - Letters of congratulation (Folder 572: 5-6)
      - Printed matter (Folder 572: 7)
    - Popper, Jozefina Anna (Hennie). Letters of condolence received on the occasion of her death, 1985 (Folder 572: 8-9)
  - Testimonials, 1936-1945 (Folder 573: 1)
- WRITINGS BY OTHERS II, 1946-1993 (Box 573-581)
  Articles, correspondence, drafts of books, and essays, arranged alphabetically by name of author. Includes relevant correspondence
  - Alderson, John (Folder 573: 2)
  - Angelidis, Thomas (Folder 573: 3)
  - Bakshov, Nadim (Folder 573: 4)
  - Barnhart, Joe (Folder 573: 5)
  - Bartels, Hinrich (Folder 573: 6)
  - Bartley, William Warren, III (Folder 573: 7)
  - Beade, Pedro (Folder 573: 8)
  - Beausoleil, Jean-Roch (Folder 573: 9)
  - Belis, Marianne (Folder 573: 10)
  - Berning, Hugo (Folder 573: 11)
  - Bickhard, Mark (Folder 573: 12)
  - Blandino, Giovanni (Folder 573: 13)
  - Blaukopf, Kurt (Folder 573: 14)
  - Boyer, Miguel (Folder 573: 15)
  - Carrington, Samantha (Folder 573: 16)
  - Caton, Hiram (Folder 574: 1)
  - Chan, C. W. (Folder 574: 2)
  - Cleary, John J. (Folder 574: 3)
  - Collett, M. J. (Folder 574: 4)
  - Connelly, James (Folder 574: 5)
  - Cubeddu, Raimondo (Folder 574: 6)
  - Dornbusch, Tim (Folder 574: 7)
  - Dover, Gabriel (Folder 574: 8)
  - Ebringer, A. (Folder 574: 9)
  - Eccles, John (Folder 574: 10-11)
  - Eidlin, Fred (Folder 574: 12)
  - Englander, Jean-Loup (Folder 574: 13)
  - Espada, Joao Carlos (Folder 574: 14-15)
  - Esterson, Allen (Folder 575: 1)
  - Farr, James (Folder 575: 2)
  - Farrell, Robert (Folder 575: 3)
  - Feuer, Lewis S. (Folder 575: 4)
  - Feyerabend, Paul (Folder 575: 5)
  - Freeman, Derek (Folder 575: 6-7)
  - Gillies, Donald (Folder 575: 8)
  - Gilroy, Jack (Folder 575: 9)
  - Giuculescu, Alexandre (Folder 575: 10)
  - Golz, Walter (Folder 575: 11)
  - Good, Irving John (Folder 575: 12)
  - Grattan-Guinness, I. (Folder 575: 13)
  - Groot, Adriaan D. de (Folder 575: 14)
  - Gumanski, Leon (Folder 575: 15)
  - Guy, Bernard (Folder 575: 16)
  - Halpern, Leopold (Folder 575: 17)
  - Hark, Michel ter (Folder 575: 18)
  - Hemmerlin, Emmanuel (Folder 575: 19)
  - Hocevar, H. Emil (Folder 576: 1)
  - Hook, Sidney (Folder 576: 2)
  - Hudson, Keith (Folder 576: 3)
  - Hussey, Trevor (Folder 576: 4)
  - Hutcheon, Pat Duffy (Folder 576: 5)
  - Jacobs, Struan (Folder 576: 6)
  - James, Roger (Folder 576: 7)
  - Kahn, Charles H. (Folder 576: 8)
  - Kandler, Otto (Folder 576: 9)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Folder 576: 10)
  - Kiesewetter, Hubert (Folder 576: 11)
  - Kuhne, Jozef (Folder 576: 12)
  - Kvaka, Juraj (Folder 576: 13)
  - Langer, Jaroslav (Folder 576: 14)
  - Leeson, Robert (Folder 576: 15)
  - Lighthill, James (Folder 576: 16)
  - Lindh, Allan G. (Folder 576: 17)
  - Lovelock, James E. (Folder 576: 18)
  - Makinde, M. Akin (Folder 576: 19)
  - Malzkorn, Wolfgang (Folder 576: 20)
  - Mansfeld, Jaap (Folder 576: 21)
  - Marcucci, Silvestro (Folder 576: 22)
  - Marshall, Trevor (Folder 576: 23)
  - Mayer, Wilfried (Folder 576: 24)
  - Mayr, Ernst (Folder 576: 25)
  - Menger, Karl (Folder 577: 1)
  - Milford, Karl (Folder 577: 2)
  - Milford, Peter (Folder 577: 3)
  - Miller, David William (Folder 577: 4)
  - Mitchell, Peter (Folder 577: 5)
  - Modolfsky, Naomi (Folder 577: 6)
  - Mould, Richard (Folder 577: 7)
  - Mourelatos, Alexander P. D. (Folder 577: 8)
  - Mugur-Schachter, Mioara (Folder 577: 9)
  - Munz, Peter (Folder 577: 10)
  - Mura, Alberto (Folder 577: 11)
  - Musgrave, Alan (Folder 577: 12)
  - Nieland, Joop F. (Folder 577: 13)
  - Niemann, Hans-Joachim (Folder 577: 14)
  - Noske, Rainer (Folder 577: 15)
  - O'Farrell, Anthony G. (Folder 577: 16)
  - Pera, Marcello (Folder 577: 17)
  - Petroni, Angelo (Folder 577: 18)
  - Philip, John (Folder 577: 19)
  - Pickel, Andreas (Folder 578: 1)
  - Platnick, Norman I. (Folder 578: 2)
  - Post, Evert Jan (Folder 578: 3)
  - Prokhovnik, Simon J. (Folder 578: 4)
  - Radford, Michael (Folder 578: 5)
  - Radnitzky, Gerard (Folder 578: 6)
  - Rautenhaus, Heinrich (Folder 578: 7)
  - Reda, Clementina Gily (Folder 578: 8)
  - Reines, Brandon P. (Folder 578: 9)
  - Renyi, Alfred (Folder 578: 10)
  - Reuter, Edzard (Folder 578: 11)
  - Rolland, Olivier (Folder 578: 12)
  - Rossler, Otto E. (Folder 578: 13)
  - Russell, Michael J. (Folder 578: 14)
  - Sadovsky, Vadim (Folder 578: 15)
  - Sah, Raaj K. (Folder 578: 16)
  - Salamun, Kurt (Folder 578: 17)
  - Scerri, Eric (Folder 578: 18)
  - Schafer, Lothar (Folder 578: 19)
  - Scheer, Jens (Folder 578: 20)
  - Scheuch, Erwin K. (Folder 578: 21)
  - Schoch, Daniel (Folder 578: 22)
  - Schrodinger, Erwin (Folder 579: 1)
  - Scott, Charles (Folder 579: 2)
  - Selleri, Franco (Folder 579: 3)
  - Sen, Satyabrata (Folder 579: 4)
  - Settle, Thomas W. (Folder 579: 5)
  - Sheridan, William (Folder 579: 6)
  - Sikorav, Jean-Louis (Folder 579: 7)
  - Simkin, Colin (Folder 579: 8)
  - Simon, Julian (Folder 579: 9)
  - Southwood, H. M. (Folder 579: 10)
  - Spedicato, Emilio (Folder 579: 11)
  - Stapp, Henry P. (Folder 579: 12)
  - Stokes, Geoff (Folder 579: 13)
  - Temple, George (Folder 579: 14)
  - Tomita, Kazuhisa (Folder 579: 15)
  - Treder, Hans-Jurgen (Folder 579: 16)
  - Trouble, Michel (Folder 579: 17)
  - Truesdell, Clifford (Folder 580: 1)
  - Vigier, Jean-Pierre (Folder 580: 2)
  - Vlastos, Gregory (Folder 580: 3-4)
  - Vogelsang, Rudolf (Folder 580: 5)
  - Wachter, Michael (Folder 580: 6)
  - Wachtershauser, Gunter (Folder 580: 7-9)
  - Wachtershauser, Gunter (Contd.) (Folder 581: 1-3)
  - Weinberg, Steven (Folder 581: 4)
  - Weingartner, Paul (Folder 581: 5)
  - Yabrov, Alexander (Folder 581: 6)
  - Yuen, Hoh-Kun (Folder 581: 7)
  - Zycha, Harald (Folder 581: 8)
- FORMERLY CLOSED MATERIAL, 1959-1994 (Box 582-583)
  Letters of recommendation, 1959-1993, and writings, 1986-1994
  - Letters of recommendation written by Popper on behalf of others, 1959-1993
    - A (Folder 582: 1)
    - B (Folder 582: 2-6)
    - C (Folder 582: 7)
    - D (Folder 582: 8)
    - E (Folder 582: 9)
    - F (Folder 582: 10-11)
    - G (Folder 582: 12-14)
    - H (Folder 582: 15-19)
    - J (Folder 582: 20)
    - K (Folder 582: 21-23)
    - L (Folder 583: 1-4)
    - M (Folder 583: 5-6)
    - O (Folder 583: 7)
    - S (Folder 583: 8-14)
    - W (Folder 583: 15-17)
    - Z (Folder 583: 18)
  - Writings, 1986-1994
    - "A New Interpretation of Darwinism,", 1986 June 12
      First Peter Medawar Lecture, The Royal Society, London, England
      - Notes and outlines (Folder 583: 19)
      - Holograph (incomplete) (Folder 583: 20)
      - Typescript (Folder 583: 21)
      - Correspondence, 1986 (Folder 583: 22)
    - "On Excess Content: A Reply to Elby" (with David W. Miller), 1994 August 26 (Folder 583: 23)